[{"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "9"}, {"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "1"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "5"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [5, 4, 8], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "9"}, {"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "5"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "6"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [8, 1, 4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "7"}, {"type": "num", "val": "6"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "2"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "5"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4, 3, 4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "8"}, {"type": "num", "val": "8"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "3"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "9"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 6, 5], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "7"}, {"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "1"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "4"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4, 3, 8], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "9"}, {"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "5"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "7"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [7, 2, 4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "7"}, {"type": "num", "val": "7"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "1"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "7"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 6, 6], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "6"}, {"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "6"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "10"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 4, 4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "8"}, {"type": "num", "val": "6"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "3"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "4"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [7, 1, 3], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}, {"type": "num", "val": "8"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "2"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "6"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [6, 4, 6], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "9"}, {"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "2"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "3"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [8, 1, 8], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}, {"type": "num", "val": "8"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "5"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "9"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [6, 4, 3], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "6"}, {"type": "num", "val": "7"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "2"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "4"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4, 2, 5], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "8"}, {"type": "num", "val": "8"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "4"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "10"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 6, 4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "7"}, {"type": "num", "val": "6"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "1"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "4"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4, 3, 5], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}, {"type": "num", "val": "8"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "3"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "5"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [8, 2, 5], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}, {"type": "num", "val": "7"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "3"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "9"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4, 6, 4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "6"}, {"type": "num", "val": "7"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "4"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "5"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [5, 1, 3], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}, {"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "5"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "9"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [6, 4, 4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "7"}, {"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "2"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "7"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 5, 8], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "8"}, {"type": "num", "val": "6"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "3"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "9"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 6, 3], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "6"}, {"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "4"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "8"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 4, 6], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}, {"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "5"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "10"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [5, 5, 4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "6"}, {"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "2"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "4"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4, 2, 7], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "6"}, {"type": "num", "val": "7"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "5"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "10"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [1, 5, 2], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "7"}, {"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "5"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "8"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4, 3, 4], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "9"}, {"type": "num", "val": "7"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "2"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "6"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [5, 4, 5], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "7"}, {"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "3"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "6"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [4, 3, 6], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "8"}, {"type": "num", "val": "9"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "1"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "7"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [2, 6, 8], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}, {"body": [{"title": "数的分合", "stem": "看图填数", "content": [[{"type": "num", "val": "10"}, {"type": "num", "val": "10"}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}, {"type": "symbol", "val": "split"}], [{"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}, {"type": "num", "val": "5"}, {"type": "input", "val": ""}], [{"type": "symbol", "val": "sum"}], [{"type": "num", "val": "8"}]], "type": "num-open-close", "keyboardtype": "num"}], "answers": [7, 3, 5], "knowledges": ["10以内数的合与分"], "resource": "", "type": "填空", "explain": "", "level": "3", "number": "1-1-12-03"}]